sharekna.com 2013-04-19

# Sharekna :: The free online Video and Photo sharing for the Arab world

Al Bawaba is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy (together with our Conditions and any other documents referred to in it) sets out the basis on which any personal data Al Bawaba collects from you, or that you provide to Al Bawaba, will be processed by Al Bawaba. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. 

  * Privacy statement  
In order for Al Bawaba to deliver an effective service to you it is necessary for Al Bawaba to store personal information about you. 

Al Bawaba will treat all information supplied by you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy only applies to this website and you should refer to the privacy policy of any third party website that you access in connection with this website, whether by means of hyperlink or otherwise. 

Information supplied to Al Bawaba will be processed and stored on a secure server and may be used in connection with future visits to this website to facilitate easy repeated use. Transaction processes will use data, encrypted using a Secured Socket Layer ("SSL") session. You should ensure that your version of your web browser supports SSL. 

  * Data protection  
Al Bawaba may collect and process the following data about you: 
    * information that you provide by filling in forms on the website including without limitation your name and email address. This includes information provided at the time of registration. Al Bawaba may also ask you for information when you report a problem with the website, 
    * correspondence that you may have sent to Al Bawaba, 
    * surveys used for research or marketing purposes, 
    * details of your visits to the website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, other communication data. 
  
Information that Al Bawaba receives or gathers (whether or not under this Privacy Policy), may be used by Al Bawaba, its employees and/or agents to: 
    * identify you when you re-visit the website, 
    * help administer any accounts, services and products offered by Al Bawaba from time to time, 
    * help Al Bawaba to detect fraud or losses and to monitor the use of the Website, 
    * keep you updated as to developments in the services offered on the Website and/or by Al Bawaba, and 
    * for Al Bawaba marketing purposes and/or the marketing purposes of selected third parties which Al Bawaba feels may be of interest to you. 
  * Cookies  
The website makes use of cookies. Cookies are data files that are stored on your computer's hard drive and keep records of your visit to a website. They allow Al Bawaba to recognise you and tailor your visit to suit your individual preferences. You may be able to configure your web browser to prevent the use of cookies although some functions or services may not be available. If any third party websites you can access through the website use cookies, Al Bawaba cannot access or control that. If you want to know more about cookies you could try visiting [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

Version 0.2 - © 2008 - 2013 Sharekna
